<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 DAYS BACK TO HEALTHY</string>
    <string name='title0'>Make a plan</string>
    <string name='title1'>Add a glass of water</string>
    <string name='title2'>Try this recipe</string>
    <string name='title3'>Back of on booze</string>
    <string name='title4'>Take a walk</string>
    <string name='title5'>Add vegetables</string>
    <string name='title6'>Break up goals</string>
    <string name='title7'>Make a plan</string>
    <string name='title8'>Try this recipe</string>
    <string name='title9'>Get enough sleep</string>
    <string name='title10'>Plan healthy snacks</string>
    <string name='title11'>Go meatless today</string>
    <string name='title12'>Treat yourself</string>
    <string name='title13'>Try this recipe</string>
    <string name='title14'>Make a plan</string>
    <string name='title15'>Add vegetables</string>
    <string name='title16'>Add a glass of Water</string>
    <string name='title17'>Take a walk</string>
    <string name='title18'>Try this recipe</string>
    <string name='title19'>Go meatless today</string>
    <string name='title20'>Share a meal with people you love</string>
    <string name='title21'>Make a plan</string>
    <string name='title22'>Back off on booze</string>
    <string name='title23'>Try this recipe</string>
    <string name='title24'>Get enough sleep</string>
    <string name='title25'>Opt for whole grains</string>
    <string name='title26'>Treat yourself</string>
    <string name='title27'>Plan healthy snacks</string>
    <string name='title28'>Try this recipe</string>
    <string name='title29'>Add vegetables</string>
    <string name='desc0'>At the beginning of each week, make a plan to help you get back on track. Write out the meals (or even just the dinners) you plan to have this week.</string>
    <string name='desc1'>Staying hydrated is super important, especially when you are trying to get back on track. There are tons of health benefits associated with drinking enough water, from clearer skin to a better mood..</string>
    <string name='desc2'>Swap traditional noodles and save on carbs with our Zucchini Noodles with Avocado Pesto and Shrimp recipe. This dish is loaded with healthy fat and satisfying protein.</string>
    <string name='desc3'>Take one day (or more, if you like) off from drinking. Though it can be tempting to have a nightly glass of wine or a fun summery cocktail, your body will thank you for the occasional break</string>
    <string name='desc4'>Make your morning coffee to-go and start your day with a walk, or go for a stroll as a family after dinner..</string>
    <string name='desc5'>Vegetables are the cornerstone of a healthy eating pattern, and adding them to what you already eat can help you boost your daily intake.</string>
    <string name='desc6'>It is ok to have big goals, but it can be helpful to break them up into things that are shorter term and more tangible. Try making daily or weekly goals.</string>
    <string name='desc7'>At the beginning of each week, make a plan to help you get back on track. Write out the meals (or even just the dinners) you plan to have this week..</string>
    <string name='desc8'>Plant-based mains have never been so craveable as our Mushroom Shawarma with Yogurt Tahini Sauce. </string>
    <string name='desc9'>This one is easier said than done, but there are some serious health benefits to catching enough zzz To help you practice good sleep hygiene.</string>
    <string name='desc10'>Get ahead of hunger and save on money and time by planning out healthy snacks in advance.</string>
    <string name='desc11'>Following a more plant-based diet is a great way to eat healthier and save money. Bonus: it also helps you have a more earth-friendly eating pattern.</string>
    <string name='desc12'>Allow yourself some wiggle room in your plan to treat yourself occasionally. </string>
    <string name='desc13'>Have a fresh and savory meal to start your day with this Baby Kale Breakfast Salad with Quinoa and Strawberries.</string>
    <string name='desc14'>At the beginning of each week, make a plan to help you get back on track. Write out the meals (or even just the dinners) you plan to have this week.</string>
    <string name='desc15'>Vegetables are the cornerstone of a healthy eating pattern, and adding them to what you already eat can help you boost your daily intake.</string>
    <string name='desc16'>There are tons of health benefits associated with drinking enough water, from clearer skin to a better mood.</string>
    <string name='desc17'>Adding bouts of movement, like walking, biking or gardening, throughout your day can help you get closer to the daily recommended amount of activity.</string>
    <string name='desc18'>With this adapted version of vegetarian Eggplant Curry, you won’t even miss the meat.</string>
    <string name='desc19'>Following a more plant-based diet is a great way to eat healthier and save money.</string>
    <string name='desc20'>There are so many great reasons to carve out time for meals as a family, or with friends.</string>
    <string name='desc21'>You can  make a plan for exercise to help up your movement.</string>
    <string name='desc22'>Alcohol can absolutely be part of a healthy eating pattern, but moderation is key.</string>
    <string name='desc23'>Say goodbye to standard pasta noodles and hello to refreshing zoodles with this Zucchini Noodle Primavera.</string>
    <string name='desc24'>Set boundaries with technology and food before bed to help you fall asleep better and feel refreshed in the morning.</string>
    <string name='desc25'>The Dietary Guidelines for Americans suggest making sure that at least half of the grains you eat each day are whole grains.</string>
    <string name='desc26'>Whether it is a better-for-you twist on a classic treat or simply something you are craving, giving yourself flexibility is key to long term success.</string>
    <string name='desc27'>Having snacks like mixed nuts, veggies and hummus or fruit and cheese slices ready in advance will also make the healthy choice.</string>
    <string name='desc28'>Salads don’t get much more comforting than our Spinach Salad with Roasted Sweet Potatoes, White Beans and Basil.</string>
    <string name='desc29'> Add spinach to smoothies or onions and peppers to tomato sauce, or make a side salad to pair with your meal for a delicious veggie boost.</string>
    <string name="expand_button">Expand Button to view description of each day</string>
    <string name="days_30">30 Days of Healthy Life</string>

</resources>